83.166.169.240 2010-04-23

# PacktPub.com Privacy Policy | Packt Publishing Book Store

> _Updated 25 Feb 2004_

**Security of your Personal Information**  
PacktPub.com is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When we transmit sensitive information over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

**Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To deliver goods to you that you ordered directly from us 
  * To deliver electronic services, such as newsletters or downloads that you request 
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you. 
  * To alert you to amendments, corrections, special offers, updated information and other new services from Packt Publishing, if you so request. 
  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate. 

At this point we do not merge usage information with registration information to create personalized content on our web sites. However we may choose to do that in the future, in which case we will offer you the option to opt out of this service. 

This policy applies to all web sites and email services provided by Packt Publishing. By using these web sites you consent to the general terms and conditions of usage and to the terms of this privacy policy.

Packt Publishing Ltd  32 Lincoln Road  Olton Birmingham B27 6PA  United Kingdom  T : +44 121 683 1170 F: +44 121 683 1171

**Use of Cookies**  
When you visit a Packt Publishing website, a cookie is often placed on your machine (if it is set up to accept cookies) or an existing cookie is read if you have visited the site previously. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above. We also use cookies to collect information on which newsletter links are clicked by customers. This information is used to ensure we are sending information customers want to read. It is collected in aggregate form and never linked with your personal information. Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookie on our site. This technology tells us how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a web page. We do not use this technology to access your personally identifiable information; it is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about Packt Publishing website usage. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies but do not allow other companies to place clear gifs on our sites. 

**Sharing Your Personal Information**  
As a matter of principle we do not sell information we retain about you to any third parties. We do share limited information in the following limited and specific circumstances: 

  * We use agents to perform certain operational functions such as warehousing, credit-card processing, shipment etc. We pass on to these partners only the information they need about you to perform the service required, and they are not allowed to use this information for any other purpose. 
  * We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Packt Publishing or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Packt Publishing and its family of Web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Packt Publishing employees, customers, or members of the public. 

Control of your Personal Information When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, Packt Publishing will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. At the time of registering for some services, you will be given the option to opt out of receiving email from Packt Publishing beyond the scope of the specific service in question. If you do not opt out at this point, we may send you what we in good faith believe to be useful and relevant information about our products and services. You can view the information that we retain about you by logging in to your account at [www. **Packt** Pub.com/account](http://www.packtpub.com/account). At any time you can change your preferences for how or if we contact you, or change the information that we hold. For email registrations where you do not have a full account and password set up, subscription options can be changed and authenticated through email. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, we request this information when you are registering before ordering products from Packtpub.com, downloading or viewing limited-access content, entering a contest, ordering email newsletters. In each circumstance we try to limit the information we request to the minimum required to deliver the service to you. We also use various standard technologies such as cookies to track user activity on our sites. 

|   |    
---|---|---
